[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
EAT MY VOW
[Legoshi] Here you go.
Tsukimi Udon with extra dandelion.
[Haru] Wow! [chuckles]
Mmm. Smells good.
Hey, you got a sec to sit down?
Uh...
Well, is that okay with you?
She was my senior in high school.
Legoshi, you've got yourself a girlfriend?
- Uh...
- [both chuckle]
Well, hey, thanks for coming out
for my birthday.
Yeah, of course. I wanted to see you.
Plus, I was curious to see what kind
of place was lucky enough to hire you.
It's cute. And I like the seats
for small animals.
[Legoshi] Mmm.
Thanks for the food!
- Ah!
- What?
Uh, nothing. I just think that
that's a good idea,
breaking up the egg in the noodles first.
What? You don't do that?
You're missing out.
It's served in the same bowl for a reason.
[Legoshi] Mmm.
[blowing]
[slurps]
[chews, gulps]
This is delicious!
[Legoshi laughs]
[blowing, slurps]
[Haru chuckles]
- [Haru slurps]
- Haru.
There's something I need to tell you.
I... I wanted to say this
at the bus station, but...
Can I tell you now?
Mmm?
The reason I dropped out of school...
[slurps]
Well, it's because I ate Louis' right leg.
[Haru sighs] Really?
[sighs] I'm trying to eat here, you know?
- Huh?
- [Haru grunting]
- Uh... [splutters] Hey. Haru, were are you--
Hmm?
- Present time.
- What?
We are going to buy you
a birthday present, okay?
You can tell me more about it on the way.
- While we're on our date!
- Uh--
Uh...
- You can take off early today.
- [Legoshi chuckles nervously]
[pleasant music playing]
Oh, look at the dinosaurs!
- Hmm? Yeah. Uh...
- Which one do you want?
[Haru] Wow, they're huge!
Look at that one.
- Some were even bigger. Yeah.
- Yeah? I never knew that.
[Haru pants]
- Over here! How do I look?
- [Legoshi chuckles] You look good.
I told her everything. I had to.
- Open your mouth.
- That mine?
I told her about the fight with Riz
after I found him out.
I told her how I ate Louis' leg,
with his permission,
in a desperate attempt to win that fight.
[Haru] Wow. That was enough
to cause withdrawal?
Mmm. Sometimes I can't control myself
when I come into contact with herbivores.
Oh, but I-- I'm fine right now. I promise.
Hmm. Then, how about some mint?
- Hmm?
- It has a relaxing effect.
I didn't know that. Hmm.
[Haru] I've always tried
to stay out of Legoshi's business.
I never asked what he was up to.
Hmm. Maybe I was too scared to find out.
Hmm. That is nice.
Look! It's the Cherryton windmill.
And that's where
you pulled out your fangs, right?
[Legoshi] Mmm.
- Yeah, somewhere around there. Yeah.
- [chuckles]
[Haru sighs deeply]
This sucks, though. This big old fence.
Well, they have to have it.
Imagine if there was an incident
while someone was up in the air.
I know that, but it ruins the mood.
You really feel that way?
- You're not just being nice?
- What?
I know he said I could,
but I did still eat a person's leg.
That has to change
how you see me. Doesn't it?
Hmm...
I guess I could scream and cry,
or curse you out
if you really wanted me to.
But, I don't know,
maybe you've had enough of that already.
And I don't care anyway.
Our relationship is just ours.
I have no intention of meddling
in your friendship with Louis.
And my life hasn't been noble enough
for me to criticize you for anything.
For carnivores and herbivores
to understand each other,
we need to face each other with open eyes.
And hearts.
So, that's what I've decided to do.
And so, there's somewhere
I'd like to go together.
- The market.
- What?
- Take me to the Black Market.
- I can't do that.
I want to know everything
about the boy I love.
[Legoshi exhales softly]
[Haru] So, is it a date?
[Legoshi] Haru,
we really shouldn't do this.
It's fine. I'm not scared.
Uh-- Hey, stop for a second.
[exclaims]
- [muffled] What are you doing?
- At least hide your face.
[exhales, grumbles] This is my favorite
sweater, and you've stretched it all out.
I'm sorry, but your life
means more than a sweater.
Oh, stop freaking out.
[gasps] Now I can't see anything!
[Haru groaning, grumbling]
Come on! Ugh! Move your hand!
- I--
- Sorry, but no.
I can't see like this!
[indistinct chattering]
[upbeat music playing]
Fresh cuts on sale! Step right up!
You okay?
[gasps] Haru! Wait!
Hey, big guy. I bet you love a good deal!
- We got juicy mixed sausages for canines!
- Come and get your goat meat!
- We got legs, we got thighs, we got wings.
- [seller] Oh, if it isn't the young wolf.
[Legoshi] Hey. It's been a while.
I have fresh bamboo grass here,
if you'd like some.
[Legoshi] Not today,
but maybe next time. [chuckles nervously]
[sellers shouting indistinctly]
- How about a bag of fresh rat?
- No, thank you. [gasps]
[gasps, trembles]
[slurps, grunts]
Huh? [growling]
[Haru panting]
[customer panting]
[customer rapid panting]
[Haru rapid panting]
[snarling]
[Haru pants, gasps]
Stay with me! Please,
you can't go running off like that.
[grunts, scoffs]
Hey! Stop pulling!
We should just go home--
Haru?
Haru.
[whispers] It's dangerous here.
- Over there.
- Hmm?
RABBIT
What? You can't be serious.
I-- Wait, wait, wait!
RABBIT
[Haru] You know...
I hate myself for being
such a weak creature.
Even if it is just an accident of birth.
[sighs] I always have.
That's why I wound up turning to sex.
So, somehow, I came to decide
that I could only be
someone's equal in bed.
Pathetic. [sighs]
I was was such a mess back then.
I was barely keeping it together.
But not now.
Now, I'm safe.
I don't have to be reckless.
Because now...
I have you by my side.
Um, my, uh...
My stomach feels kind of weird.
Don't go getting hungry
at a time like this.
Yeah, you're surrounded by food,
but, come on!
It's not that.
Legoshi...
will you kiss me?
Right here?
Please kiss me.
Let go of everything else out there.
Only you and I exist now.
- I can't.
- [gasps]
I told you.
Beasts with a record of prior devouring
can't marry herbivores.
I don't care about marriage.
It's enough that we understand each other.
Not to me, it isn't.
I want us to build a family together.
I want kids!
So, I just think it's inappropriate
for me to be physical with you!
Huh?
I turned 18 today. I'm a man now.
- I should act like it.
- [scoffs]
Listen. My mom and grandpa
aren't legally recognized as my family,
so I... I get how hard all this can be.
And I'd rather wait,
till I've had some more time
to figure this out.
- [growls] Stop!
- [seller] Uh, hey there?
Can I help you folks with anything, or...
- How much would it be for me?
- [both gasp]
- Haru!
- How much would my meat cost?
- Name your price and the wolf will buy it!
- What are you saying?
I'm saying I don't understand
what you're saying.
You've never made less sense!
- Sorry, sir! It's just a joke.
- Really? So this is all a joke to you?
- I'm finished!
- With what?
- Well, if--
- Hey! It's dangerous!
Haru! Whoa!
You know, she actually would fetch
a pretty penny.
Hmm.
- [Lycaon shuddering]
- [rapid clicking]
[Louis sighs]
[Louis] I can't concentrate.
- What is he--
- [rapid clicking continues]
- [shuddering]
- Ah. Meat withdrawal symptoms.
- Oh, dear.
- [breath trembling]
No. He would be sweating more
if that were the case.
- Hey.
- Huh?
Have a mint. It may help calm your nerves.
- What?
- Here.
Uh...
Ah, right. Sorry, buddy. Thanks.
[exclaims]
Is that...
Uh, the Kines?
[Chloe] Of course I can do it.
But if we're found out,
your father will let you off scot-free,
and I'd be finished.
You understand
what I'd be putting on the line for you.
Yes, I most certainly do, which is why
we're going to keep our mouths shut.
[exhales]
Yeah, yeah. You're just lucky
I find it interesting.
Hmm.
So, this is the stuff?
And what do you need it analyzed for?
It's just for school. A little project.
You're going with that? Okay.
[sighs]
Whatever. I'll have the results
for you next week.
And, hey, don't forget this
when you take over.
Oh, I wouldn't dream of it.
I'll get you a better budget.
And maybe a smoking area.
[chuckles]
I'll remember that. Don't let me down.
[Louis] Why does everyone I speak to
always have to be so difficult?
[buzzing]
[exclaims softly]
[Louis] Including her,
but in a different way.
Your visual acuity is wonderful.
Ew! Ew! Oh, gross! I'm so scared of bugs!
Well, that didn't stop you
from crushing it barehanded.
You're not embarrassed
of your hunting instincts, are you?
No, it's not that.
They really do creep me out!
[Louis] Juno and I have begun
to meet regularly for tea.
Once, perhaps twice a month.
[sighs] Ever since...
But we never speak of it.
We never hint at it.
We stick primarily to small talk.
Tell me something.
I've been doing some thinking
and I wondered,
you come for tea
every time if I invite you,
but it's so hard to tell
if you even enjoy it, so...
I can't help but wonder why.
Just keeping up
with your youthful spontaneity, Juno.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
Why come if you're just going to
look down on me?
You're 17 now, aren't you?
An age where you want to explore
many different things.
Things like flirting with an older guy,
or just talking to an herbivore.
And if you can tackle both at once,
I imagine that's convenient.
Oh! You are literally
so mean to me! [groans]
Mean, logical, skinny.
The more I think about it,
the more I realize
you're not even my type to begin with.
So, why did I end up with such a big,
stupid, idiot crush on you?!
[Louis] I don't believe this woman has
ever had an unvoiced thought in her life!
It's like she can say or do
whatever she wants, and get away with it.
This one girl is more terrifying
than Legoshi or the entire Shishi-Gumi!
Well, to be frank,
I don't want someone like you either.
- Come on, let's get out of here.
- What? No, we just got here.
It's fine. 'Kay? Let's go.
Aw.
[mellow music playing]
[Juno] Hey, Louis.
You don't have
any other plans today, do you?
I do.
- I'm meeting my fiancée.
- Huh?
I could have sword you knew.
My marriage partner
was decided for me many years ago.
She's the heiress
to another large company,
and she's a red deer just like I am.
- [gasps softly]
- Do you see now?
It's true that I have no ulterior motives
in meeting with you.
[Juno sighs softly]
Earlier, you told me
I shouldn't be embarrassed
about my hunting instincts, didn't you?
Well, if you run away from me,
it'll make me want to chase you.
I know you still think about it.
That kiss we shared.
I saw the way
you were looking at my straw.
How I was biting it.
I bet you wish that was you instead.
All worn down.
- [Louis grunts]
- [groaning]
Now, now, Juno.
Big shot predators
shouldn't blush like that.
That hurts!
[grunts] Get away from me!
- Bye, then.
- [Juno] Huh?
Well, there's no way things
will work out with your fiancée.
Not if it's an arranged marriage!
How would you know?
Our relationship is healthy.
And not at all desperate.
UDON BEBEBE
[Juno crying]
So, uh...
Hey, Juno?
Can you at least tell me
why you're crying?
We haven't seen each other in a while,
so I don't know what's going on.
Uh... Did something happen
at the drama club?
[crying]
I'm impressed you tracked me down.
Oh, everyone in the club
knows you work here!
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- [continues crying]
Legoshi, I had no idea
you were such a ladies' man.
I'm not! She's a junior
from my high school drama club.
- [Sunaga] You two suit each other.
- No, we don't-- [sighs]
I just don't know what to do
with myself anymore. [sniffles]
Legoshi, you're, like, the only person
I can rely on now.
Well, I'm happy to listen,
if you wanna talk.
But, uh,
I don't know if I'm the best person
to be giving out advice.
No, you're the perfect person!
You know all about
interspecies relationships!
Huh?
I'm in love. And I need advice!
This whole mess started last year,
right before the Festival of the Meteor.
We were alone in the rehearsal room,
and I wound up pushing him to the ground.
I really wasn't interested then,
because he wasn't my type.
[high-speed] But after I went to visit him
on my own, it hit me.
I couldn't stop thinking
about how beautiful Louis is.
At the graduation ceremony,
he was all composed.
He also had this vulnerable look
that was so gorgeous.
And then I kissed him. But he told me
to forget about it and walked off...
[continues indistinctly in high speed]
- [in normal speed] So, what do you think?
- [standby beeping]
Oh. Le-- Legoshi?
Oh, no. I think he's broken.
- Um... Legoshi!
- [gasps]
Sorry. My brain wasn't able
to keep up with your plotline.
It's okay. I blindsided you.
I thought that might shock you
a little bit.
If it helps any,
I'm surprised at myself too.
It's almost embarrassing, you know?
I didn't want to fall for Louis like this.
[Legoshi] I'm mostly surprised
that you went in for the kiss
on the very same day
you realized you had feelings for him.
And all this time,
I still haven't kissed Haru.
- [sighs]
- Even though she...
Talking about all this has filled
my head up with his stupid face even more.
And I guess you must have noticed
when I walked in.
Huh? Noticed what?
I've put on a lot of weight recently.
Little by little, ever since
I realized I had feelings for him.
Just thinking about him makes me
so hungry, I can barely stand it.
It's terrifying, isn't it?
I thought when you fell in love
with someone,
your heart was supposed to skip a beat.
So, why does my stomach rumble?
[sighs]
I think that...
somewhere deep down, I really do
just want to eat him after all.
And it feels so shameful to mix up
love and appetite like this.
Do you see why you're the only one
I can turn to?
I guess. I've worried about this stuff
a lot myself--
But I have something you don't have!
- For me, being a carnivore is a weapon!
- Huh?
I might be able to win him over
with the kind of excitement
herbivore girls can't offer!
- [chuckles nervously] Now, that's--
- Try to think about it like this.
When you see that pipsqueak's...
[scoffs] What's her name? Uh...
Haru's herbivorous tendencies,
it's not like they annoy you, right?
You actually like them, right?
Uh... Yeah, I do!
So, you see?
Then, don't you think
Haru feels the same about you?
Yeah. No. I don't think
that's quite the case.
Oh, okay. Well,
how did you win her over then?
Sincerity?
- Or, no. Persistence?
- Wha...
You have to be kidding.
Legoshi, love is a competition!
Are you really so confident?
You're completely assured
that Haru is yours
with no one else
in the picture at all forever?
What? I-- I've never really
thought about it.
Is that what made her so angry?
[parrot] Tweet-tweet! Hello there, pals!
You're on Peepee's Parrot Channel!
And I got a question for you right here!
About those mixed-race couples
that are all the rage these days--
- Of course I'm for them!
- Of course you are.
But for real, though.
What if it was you personally?
For, against?
- Uh...
- Not other people, but you.
Oh, I guess it's a little awkward
to ask couples.
You're mistaken. We're not a couple.
What! You're not dating?
[scoffs] Well, maybe you should start.
Anyway, let's say a cute little herbivore
shows up, and she's hot for you.
- For, against?
- If it's an herbivore, I don't know--
Oh, that's a big old no, eh?
What's your reason?
The number one answer in our survey
right now, is "the crazy high risk."
Imagine you lose it
and eat your girlfriend whole.
- Your life's over!
- [Juno] Enough!
I'm a grey wolf and I'm head over heels
- for a stag right now!
- [parrot] Can I have that?
If I worry about risk,
I'll get rejected for sure!
- [parrot] Don't break it.
- Thought we were a couple?
I'm sick of everyone making assumptions
about me and my life!
Camera's expensive.
I won't let you or anyone else
decide what will make me happy!
[wailing]
[Legoshi] Oh, Juno. You're right.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE RECENT TREND
OF INTERSPECIES RELATIONSHIPS?
FOR - AGAINST
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪